[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone. <br /><br />Click \"Continue\" when you're ready to move on.","rt":318403,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":320283,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6 </sub>,  you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":7902,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":328189,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":2009,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":330200,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5 "],"rt":4540,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":334741,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1198,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":335941,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":88783,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":424726,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":5653,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":430382,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3734,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":434117,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1318,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":435437,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your  result.  If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2569,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":438008,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":827,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":438837,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["6","2"],"rt":4810,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":443647,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":741,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":444389,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":3367,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":447757,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1069,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":448828,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <b r /><br  /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3368,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":452197,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":991,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":453190,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":5773,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":458964,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1223,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":460189,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2677,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":462867,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1687,"trial_type":"feedb ack","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":464556,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":15093,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":479654,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the thing that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity und er +<sub >6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":1923,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":481582,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":9240,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":490823,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":14557,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":505383,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>?  <br />< br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":2673,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":508063,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":948,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":509014,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2220,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":511236,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":17982,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":529220,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2989,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":532213,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1142,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":533356,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the  inverse  of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":2456,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":535813,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":14750,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":550566,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"Let's review: under +<sub>6</sub>, the inverse of 0 is 0, the inverse of 1 is 5 and the inverse of 5 is 1, the inverse of 2 is 4 and the inverse of 4 is 2, and finally the inverse of 3 is 3. Do you see a relationship between an element and its inverse under +<sub>6</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","response_history":["no"],"rt":24797,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":575366,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":4211,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":579581,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub >6</sub>  1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because of this, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":40464,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":620047,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":390904,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":1010957,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2,  4, or 5  using just 3.","rt":2820,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":1013781,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":3342,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":1017125,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":975,"trial_type":"feedb ack","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":1018101,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":2158,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":1020260,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":952,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":1021213,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":2063,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":1023276,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":920,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":1024197,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Let's review: under +<sub>6</sub>, 1 and 5 are generators. However, 0, 2, 3, and 4 are not generators. Try playing with these non-generators and seeing which elements each of them does generate (i.e. which elements you can get by combining each non-generator with itself repeatedly). Do you see relationships among particular subsets of the elements that are not generators under +<sub>6</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No ._.  I am co nfused. ","response_history":["No ._. I am confused. "],"rt":12727,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":1036925,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":79383,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":1116309,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3358,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":1119668,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1062,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":1120732,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":2432,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":1123164,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":2782,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":1125948,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":4024,"trial_type":"ques tion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":1129972,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":4927,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":1134900,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":4999,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":1139900,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5 I added 4 and 1 and it was less than 9","response_history":["5 I added 4 and 1 and it was less than 9"],"rt":12454,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":1152355,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3817,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":1156173,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"Um.... I don't know....9 ?","response_history":["Um.... I don't know....9 ?"],"rt":23920,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":1180093,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4? I think, because 4 + 5 is 9? (Sorry I am bad at math and this  is very  new)","response_history":["4? I think, because 4 + 5 is 9? (Sorry I am m","4? I think, because 4 + 5 is 9? (Sorry I am bad at math and this is very new)"],"rt":19174,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":1199268,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":4591,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":1203860,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6, because 6 + 3 = 9","response_history":["6, because 6 + 3 = 9"],"rt":10519,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":1214380,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a gen erator u nder +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I dont know, still confused","response_history":["I DONT KNOW, S","I DO","I D","I dont know, still confused"],"rt":11911,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":1226292,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I am not sure ._.","response_history":["I am not sure ._."],"rt":7231,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1233524,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I dont know D:","response_history":["I dont know D: "],"rt":4880,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1238405,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I think so...","response_history":["I yt","I y","I think soo","I think so..."],"rt":7470,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1245876,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use \"+_n\", and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":86864,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1332740,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"I have no idea O_O ","response_history":["I have no idea O_O "],"rt":14984,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1347724,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"I am so far gone at this point. I really don't know... I think it can be any positive number? D: ","response_history":["I am so far gone at this point. I really don't know... I think it can be any positive number? D: "],"rt":23521,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1371245,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can y ou know  if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I dont know ._. ","response_history":["I dont know ._. "],"rt":13815,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":1385060,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":5367,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":1390428,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":5503,"trial_type":"ques tion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":1395932,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must divide n.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":5511,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":1401444,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"I really have no idea....","response_history":["I really have no idea...."],"rt":14559,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":1416004,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse  a gener ator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":7824,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":1423829,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"I dont know if it is ._. I am so confused ","response_history":["I dont know if it is ._. I am os confused ","I dont know if it is ._. I am s confused ","I dont know if it is ._. I am so confused "],"rt":12784,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":1436613,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"If an element x is  not a g enerator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":4519,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":1441132,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press \"Continue\" to continue.","rt":1550,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":1442684,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"28","response_history":["28"],"rt":2351,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":1445036,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"mul ti","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Some college, no degree","response_history":["Some college, no degree"],"rt":2664,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":1447700,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I got my GED, I didnt take much math in HS. I took college algebra and passed but I dont retain math well. ","response_history":["high ","I got my GED, I f","I got my GED, I didnt take much math in HS. SO I A","I got my GED, I didnt take much math in HS. SO I ","I got my GED, I didnt take much math i n HS. SO  I","I got my GED, I didnt take much math in HS. SO ","I got my GED, I didnt take much math in HS. SO","I got my GED, I didnt take much math in HS. S","I got my GED, I didnt take much math in HS. I took college algr","I got my GED, I didnt take much math in HS. I took college algebra and passed ut I","I got my GED, I didnt take much math in HS. I took college algebra and passed ut ","I got my GED, I didnt take much math in HS. I took college algebra and passed ut","I got my GED, I didnt take much math in HS. I took college algebra and passed u","I got my GED, I didnt take much math in HS. I took college algebra and passed BUT","I got my GED, I didnt take much math in HS. I took college algebra and passed BU","I got my GED, I didnt take much math in HS. I took college algebra and passed Bbut","I got my GED, I didnt take much math in HS. I took college algebra and passed Bbu","I got my GED, I didnt take much math in HS. I took college algebra and passed Bb","I got my GED, I di dnt take  much math in HS. I took college algebra and passed B","I got my GED, I didnt take much math in HS. I took college algebra and passed but I dont retain math e","I got my GED, I didnt take much math in HS. I took college algebra and passed but I dont retain math well. "],"rt":30607,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":1478308,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":4823,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":1483132,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept o f a math ematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - seen it used or explained","response_history":["3 - seen it used or explained"],"rt":4855,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":1487988,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3127,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":1491116,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at a ll","2 -  somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - not at all","response_history":["1 - not at all"],"rt":2432,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":1493549,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":3903,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":1497452,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","response_history":["Female"],"rt":2183,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":1499636,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your househo ld when  you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":4031,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":1503668,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","response_history":["no"],"rt":2583,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":1506252,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Sorry for losing any idea of what I was doing half way through. ","response_history":["Sorry for losing the","Sorry for losing th","Sorry for losing t","Sorry for losing any idea of what I was doing half way through. "],"rt":12433,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":1518685,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"}]